justluxe.com 2019-06-19

# Privacy Policy

##### Updated 2018

Welcome to JustLuxe. We own and operate JustLuxe.com, and protecting your information is of singular importance for our website. Read this Privacy Policy and the accompanying Terms of Service carefully before interacting with us in any significant manner, i.e., giving your information to us, using our services, interacting with our content or utilizing any of our offerings via our Websites. Interaction with our sites provides JustLuxe.com with an implied consent of your agreement to and acceptance of the policies and practices described herein.

### What Information We Obtain

Certain interactions or functions on our Websites may request users to disclose personal information, sometimes known as PII or personally identifiable information, to be included on our electronic email or postal mailing lists, make reservations, request information on our products or services, as well as our subscription services. 

To help you with some of these types of interactions via our Websites, JustLuxe may request additional types of information from you on a voluntary basis. If such information is shared with us, we won’t share specifically identifiable information of our users but may share generalized, aggregate data or so called “demographic information.” Supplying such information is optional and if you choose not to enter such information, you may still use many of these applications. If we share demographic information with third parties, we will only provide demographic data that has been aggregated.

Our Website and mobile applications may use forms for you to give us contact information (including your name, address, telephone number, and email address) so you can place orders, request information, customer support, and even interact with 3rd parties. For certain services, we may also request a credit card number, identification number, or other financial information or PII.

We receive and store any information you enter on our Websites, mobile application, or give us in any other way, including through email, telephone, or other communications with our customer service department. If you contact us for support, we may keep an internal record of what support was given.

We use your information to contact you regarding functionality changes to our products, our Websites and mobile application, newly offered JustLuxe.com services, and special offers we think you'll find valuable. If you would rather not receive this information, you’ll be able to Unsubscribe or change your preferences.

We may also use your information to present a co-branded offer with our partners or affiliates. If we collect information from you in connection with a co-branded offer, it will be clear at the point of interaction which group is collecting the information and whose privacy statement applies for that particular engagement, whether JustLuxe or our 3rd party partners.

### Data Controller and Contracting Parties

For the purposes of the General Data Protection Regulation 2016/679 (the “GDPR”), the Data Controller is LuxeMont LLC, JustLuxe.com’s parent company, registered in California, United States of America with a registered address at 501 W. Broadway, #A-321, San Diego, CA 92101.

You can contact our Data Protection Officer by sending an email to info@JustLuxe.com or by writing to:

JustLuxe.com   
Attn.: Privacy Department   
501 W. Broadway, #A-321   
San Diego, California 92101 U.S.A.

### How We Use Information We Obtain 

Like most online businesses, each time you visit our Website(s), we automatically collect your IP address and originating web page. In order to administer and optimize our Website(s) for you and to diagnose problems with our Website(s), we use your IP address to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information about you.

We use information gathered about you from our Websites or mobile application statistics (for example, your IP address, your system or device’s operating system) to help diagnose problems with our server, and to manage our Websites and mobile application. We also gather broad demographic information from this data to help us improve our Websites functionality and mobile application and make your browsing and purchasing experience more enjoyable. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information, except as necessary to prevent fraud or abuse on our system.

### Cookies

Our Websites and mobile application use cookies to keep track of your shopping cart and receipts. We also use cookies as most online companies to identify you so you don't need to log in each time you visit our Websites or mobile application. The cookies may be linked to an associated customer number, which is then associated with the information in your account.

“Cookies” are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. Like many websites, we use cookies and Pixel Tags to keep track of your activity on our Website(s) and enhance your experience. We may also use strings of code called Anonymous Identifiers that are combinations of random characters where cookies are not available (for example, when you access our Website(s) from mobile devices). 

We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, in some cases to save your password, and if you choose, to save other personal information so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit our Websites. 

You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google's Display Network ads using Google's [Ad Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads). You can opt-out of Google Analytics by using [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

Please note that not all browsers provide the ability to remove Adobe Flash "cookies" (also called "locally stored objects," or "LSOs"). You can restrict or block Adobe Flash cookies/LSOs through the [Adobe website](http://helpx.adobe.com/flash-player/kb/disable-local-shared-objects-flash.html). 

You can opt out of being targeted by certain third party advertising companies online by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp), Adobe, and/or [Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).

To find out more about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set and how to manage and delete them, visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/), or [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/).

### Other Information We Collect

When browsing our Website(s), you are not required to provide any personal information unless and until you choose to sign up for one of our e-mail newsletters, webinars, events or other services as described below. If you have opted-into receiving electronic mail communication from us, we may use your personal information to email you periodic email newsletters special offers, updated information about us or our Website(s) or ways in which we can improve your experience at our Website(s). Such emails we send to you will allow you to opt-out of future electronic communications from us.

We do not knowingly permit our Website(s) to be used by any person under the age of eighteen and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from children (meaning those younger than thirteen years of age). We store the data we collect in the Cloud and on servers owned by others. We undertake ongoing efforts to assure the integrity and security of the data on our owned servers, but cannot guarantee that the security measures we employ will always be completely effective on any 3rd party partner servers. We also cannot guarantee the absolute security of data we store on servers owned by others. We will provide electronic notice via email or on our Website(s) if we have reason to believe the integrity of our stored data has been breached or compromised, potentially permitting unauthorized third parties to access the stored data.

### Registered User Information

In some cases you may become a Registered User of our Website(s). To do so you must provide your name, address, e-mail address, a unique login name, password, and password validation, and a password hint to help you remember your password. This information is collected on the registration form for several reasons including: (1) personal identification; (2) to allow us to contact you for customer service purposes, if necessary; (3) to customize the content of our Website(s) to meet your specific needs; and (4) to make product improvements to our Website(s). 

### Information Automatically Collected

We automatically log generic information about your computer’s connection to the Internet, which we call “session data,” that is anonymous and not linked to any personal information. Session data consists of things such as IP address, operating system, location and type of browser software being used and the activities conducted by the user while on our Website(s). 

We also record the URLs (Uniform Resource Locators) of the websites you have visited prior to arriving at our Website(s) and the URLs of the destinations you visit after you leave our Websites to help us diagnose problems with our servers and lets us better administer our systems. 

You should know it is possible to determine from an IP address a visitor’s Internet Service Provider (ISP) and the approximate geographic location of his or her point of connectivity or from GPS signals sent by a mobile device. We may also use various technologies to determine location, such as sensor data from your device that may, for example, provide information on nearby Wi-Fi access points and cell towers. Third-party advertising companies may also employ technology that is used to measure the effectiveness of advertising.

### Mobile Tracking Data

If a user (including both Registered Users and visitors) places a telephone call to a number provided by our Website(s) or in communications arising out of our Website(s), we and/or marketing partners may record, track and or meter the telephone number of originating the call. We and/or our marketing partners may also store referring telephone numbers. You can ask us to delete this information at any time by contacting info@JustLuxe.com.

### Other

From time to time we may add or enhance services available on our Website(s). To the extent these services are provided and used by you, we will use the information you provide to facilitate the service requested. For example, if you submit a question on our Website(s) or by email, we will use your email address, name, nature of the question, etc. to respond to your question. We may also store such information to assist us in making our Website(s) the better and easier to use.

### Information Other Websites Collect From You

On our Websites we place links to other web sites operated by other parties. Some of these other web sites contain our brand names and trademarks and other intellectual property that we own; others do not. When you click on these links and visit these other web sites, regardless of whether or not they contain our brand names, trademarks and other intellectual property, you need to be aware that we do not control these other web sites or these other web sites’ business practices, and that this privacy policy does not apply to these other web sites. Consequently, the operators of these other web sites may collect different kinds of information about you, and may use and disclose that information in different ways than we would if it were collected on our Website(s). We encourage you to review their privacy policies and remind you that we will not be responsible for their actions.

### Sharing Your Information

When you use our Website(s) or provide us with information, we may share personal information among our corporate affiliates. We may also use aggregate data to inform these third parties as to the number of people who have seen and clicked on links to their web sites. Occasionally, we may hire a third party to act on our behalf for projects such as market-research surveys and will provide information to these third parties aggregated generalized data specifically for use in connection with these projects. We may also share your information as directed by authorities related to local, state, or federal legal causes of action, as well as other types law suits or government actions that require such information to be divulged. 

In addition to the circumstances described above, we may disclose your information as part of a validation process in the interest of preventing fraud, to provide proper accounting to our business partners (for “pay-per-click”, “pay-per-call” or “push-to-talk” advertising listings and related programs) and to validate our business metrics including number of clicks, referrer logs and other tracking information. We may also disclose your information if required to do so by law, court order, as requested by other government or law enforcement authority, or in the good faith belief that disclosure is otherwise necessary or advisable including, without limitation, to protect our rights or properties of our affiliated companies or when we have reason to believe that disclosing the information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing interference with our rights or properties, whether intentionally or otherwise, or when anyone else could be harmed by such activities. In addition, if JustLuxe or substantially all of our assets are acquired, our customer information will be transferred in connection with such acquisition to the successor owner.

### Demographic Information and Saved Listings

We use demographic and listing information to customize our Website(s) and communications to the interests of our users. We may share demographic information and listing information with marketing partners and other third parties so that they can target their advertisements and communications to the appropriate audience. Demographic and listing data we provide to advertisers and other third parties may be linked to information you have provided as a Registered User so that advertisers and third parties can target the offerings presented to you. We may capture, correct, enhance, extrapolate and store additional information and data based on information you supply, including without limitation data relating to your geographic location, IP address and provider, email and other demographic information. We may also enhance the information we collect from you with additional information collected by third parties to correct, match, enhance or complete the data you have provided. We may store and share this enhanced information on an individual or aggregated basis.

### Opt-Out

At any time, you can unsubscribe being a Registered User or a member of any of our email communications by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link and following the instructions. We reserve the right to limit our Registered Users to those who provide us with a valid email address and agree to accept e-mails. Registered Users will be notified via e-mail prior to any actions taken. After you submit personal information in connection with becoming a Registered User or other programs offered or sponsored by third parties on our Website(s), we may use such information to send you marketing emails. However, if we do so, we will provide a link on that you can click on to opt-out of receiving subsequent marketing emails generated from the same such information at any time.

Please note that changing or deleting your information otherwise opting-out of receipt of email communications from us will only change or delete the data for purposes of future activity on our Website(s) and for managing future communications. We will retain your email address on an “Opt-Out List” to help ensure that it is not incorporated into future email lists. These changes and deletions will not change or delete information that we may have already forwarded to our affiliates or any other third parties, all as provided above in this Privacy Policy. This includes user-generated content and data previously provided to us.

If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy, the practices of our Website(s), or your dealings with the Website(s), you can contact us as indicated below:

E-mail: info@JustLuxe.com

Mailing address:   
JustLuxe

Attn.: Privacy Office   
501 W. Broadway Plaza #A-321   
San Diego, CA 92101   
Telephone: (619) 615-0181

### Additional Information California Residents 

Residents of California may request a list of third parties to which certain personal information (as defined by applicable California law) obtained through a Digital Service was disclosed by JustLuxe.com during the preceding year for those third parties’ direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and want such a list, please contact us at: 

Privacy Office   
Attn: Privacy Officer   
JustLuxe.com   
501 W. Broadway #A-321   
San Diego, CA 92101 

For all requests, you must put the statement “Your California Privacy Rights” in the body of your request, as well as your name, street address, city, state, and zip code. In your request, you will need to aver that you are a California resident and provide a current California address for our response. Please also indicate within your request the name of the Digital Service or online Website to which your request applies. Please note that we cannot accept requests via the telephone, email, or by facsimile, and we are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or that do not have complete information.

### Do Not Track

JustLuxe.com does not currently take steps to respond to browsers “Do Not Track” signals as no uniform standard to respond to such signals has been developed at this time.

### EU General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”)

As an entity with global recognition, visitors to our site may include individuals within the European Economic Area (“EEA”) who may contact us and provide personal information. In order to serve these individuals, we may transfer personal information from such individuals located within the EEA (“Data Subjects”). Personal information that may be collected by us from a Data Subject in the EEA may include:

  * name
  * mailing addresses
  * telephone numbers
  * email addresses
  * payment information

We may potentially interact with local supervisory authorities in all EU states where we have business relationships with a Data Subject. Additionally, information that we collect may be transferred outside of the EEA, including to the United States, a country that has not been certified as having “adequate” security measures by the European Commission. In these cases, your personal information will be transferred only after obtaining your consent.

### Obtaining and Processing Consent

Data Subjects whose personal information is collected in the EEA may withdraw consent at any time where consent is the lawful basis for processing their information. Should a Data Subject withdraw consent for processing or otherwise object to processing that impedes our ability to comply with applicable regulations that Data Subject may be unable to enjoy our website.

### Rights of Data Subjects

  * ask what information (if any) we hold about them and why;
  * ask for a copy of such information or access to such information;
  * be informed how to correct or keep that information up to date; and
  * be informed on how we are meeting our data protection obligations.

For data collected in the EEA, Data Subjects have the additional right to:

  * request a copy of such information to be sent to a third party;
  * request that data to be erased if possible and required under the GDPR;
  * request that processing of personal information be restricted if possible and required under GDPR;
  * object to processing of personal information if possible and required under GDPR;
  * object to automated decision-making where applicable; and
  * contact a supervisory authority in the EEA to lodge a complaint regarding our processing of the 
  * Data Subject’s personal information.

When handling a data access or correction request, we will check the identity of the requesting party to ensure that he or she is the person legally entitled to make such request.

### Automated Decision Making

We do not engage in automated decision-making activities.

### Nondisclosure of Personal Information

We do not share any personal information with any nonaffiliated third parties, except when:

  * necessary to provide the service that the Data Subject has requested or authorized, or to maintain and service the customer’s account;
  * required by regulatory authorities or law enforcement officials who have jurisdiction over us or as otherwise required by any applicable law; and
  * reasonably necessary to prevent fraud and unauthorized transactions.

Our employees are prohibited, either during or subsequent to their employment, from disclosing personal information to any outside person or entity outside, including family members, except under the circumstances described above. An employee is permitted to disclose personal information only to such other employees who need to have access to such information to deliver our services.

### EEA Data Subject’s Contact

If you are located in the EEA or Switzerland and have questions or concerns regarding the processing of your personal information, you may email us at info@JustLuxe.com. Please include “Privacy” in the subject line of your email to ensure our prompt attention. You may also write to us at:

JustLuxe   
Attn.: Privacy Office   
501 W. Broadway #A-321   
San Diego, CA 92101   
619.615.0181   
USA 

If, as an EEA citizen, you believe that we have not adequately resolved any such issues, you have the right to contact the EU supervisory authority.
